KRISHNA CHAITANYA GUNDOJU

Senior coding Analyst

Ph: 7680979720 | Email | LinkedIn

ABOUT ME:

CPC®-certified medical coder with 4+ years of professional experience in application and evaluation of various code sets. In previous roles abstracted and assigned ICD and CPT codes to patient medical records, maintaining 95% accuracy. Seeking to leverage coding guidelines knowledge and strong analytical skills to implement smooth coding service.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER:

- **Medical coder:** Champ info software-from August 2015 to August 2016.
- Senior coding analyst: R1RCM-from Sep 2019 to August 2022.
- Senior executive coding auditor: EXL-from March 2023 to August 2023.

JOB RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Reviewed medical records and abstracted ICD-10, CPT and HCPCS codes
- Process of coding E&M and SDS charts.
- Coding the charts with completeness and maintaining 95% accuracy.
- Coded all Evaluation and Management services.
- Coded all procedures and diagnostic outpatient's accounts.
- Reviewed all patient records to ensure accurate coding.
- Managed outpatient coding for medical centres registered with the hospital.
- Reviewed all patient records to ensure accurate coding

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

- Vaagdevi College (KU)
 MSc (Microbiology) | June 2012
- CDC (KU) BSc (Bt.C.CA) | March 2010

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

- Good working knowledge of Surgery, E&M (OP and IP) CPT, ICD-10-CM, coding rules and standards.
- Responsible for day-to-day work allocation for team members.

- Logs & Reports are such as Production Reports, Audit Reports, and Client Requirement Reports etc.
- Responsible for priority mails from clients.
- Good knowledge of anatomy, physiology and pharmacology.
- Good understanding of medical terminology and anatomy.
- Worked in clinical trials as a blinded and unblinded coordinator.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Efficient in Software Systems: EPIC, 3M, Select Coder, Supercoder.
- Proficient using Microsoft Word, Excel,
- PowerPoint

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS:

- Certified Coder from AAPC
- Participated in a workshop conducted by
- Ventura BIO science.
- Participated In a National Seminar KU.